http://www.tnlsf.org/privacy-policy

0
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThubten Norbu Ling takes seriously its responsibilities with regard to any personal identifying information it gathers from you. This privacy policy is intended to describe how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle personal identifying information obtained through this website. What is personal identifying information?For purposes of this privacy policy, personal identifying information is defined as details collected through our website about an individual consumer, including an individual’s first and last name; a physical street address; an email address; a telephone number; a Social Security number; a driver’s license number or other government-issued identification number; an account number, credit card number or debit card number in combination with any required security code, access code or password that would permit access to a person's financial account; or any other information that permits a specific individual to be contacted physically or online. The term extends to details such as a person’s birthday, height, weight or hair color that are collected online and stored in personally identifiable form. What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering products or registering for courses and events on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience. When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To quickly process your transactions.To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect your information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We do not use Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have authorized access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we disclose any information to third-parties?Thubten Norbu Ling may provide personal identifying information to third-parties for the purpose of the Mandala magazine subscriptions or other third-party benefits made available to members of the organization. On occasion, we may also be required to provide certain personal identifying information to third-party hosts for retreats, gatherings and similar events requiring individual registration with the host. Any third-party to whom we disclose personal identifying information shall be required by contract to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the personal identifying information and to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal identifying information without your express permission. It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.
How can you review and request changes to your personal identifying information we collect?By emailing us at info@tnlsf.org;By calling us at (505) 490-6152; orBy logging in to any account you have established with us that contains such personal identifying information.What do we do in the event of a security breach resulting in the unintended disclosure of personal identifying information?In the event of a security breach resulting in the unintended disclosure of your personal identifying information, we will notify you in writing by regular mail or electronic mail in the most expedient time possible, but in no event later than 45 calendar days following discovery of the security breach unless we determine, after an appropriate investigation, that the security breach does not give rise to a significant risk of identity theft or fraud.What do we do with outdated personal identifying information?We arrange for proper disposal of records containing personal identifying information when they are no longer reasonably needed for business purposes by shredding, erasing or otherwise modifying the personal identifying information contained in the records to make the personal identifying information unreadable or undecipherable.How do we notify our online users of material changes to this privacy policy?Any material changes or amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our website on or before the effective date of the material change or amendment.How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13-years-old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control.
The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.What is the effective date of this Privacy Policy?The effective date of this Privacy Policy is April 25, 2020.
